

ANDREAS KARLSSON

JUNIOR DEVELOPER



Stockholm



https://www.andreas-k.com



070-9913982



hello@andreas-k.com

INTRODUCTION

I'm a versatile 38-year-old from Nykvarn that aspire to be a dedicated and great developer. I'm organized and not afraid to roll up my sleeves when something needs to be done. I like a challenge and see most things as opportunities to develop and learn something new.

SKILLS

JavaScript

React

Python

HTML/CSS

Driver licence

A/B

LANGUAGE

Swedish

English



HOBBIES



Running / Bicycle



Technology



Motorsport / Football

WORK EXPERIENCE

2014 - 2022

Skanska Industrial

SUPERVISOR / PROCESS OPERATOR

Computer-controlled asphalt manufacturing, repairs, maintenance, lead the staff during daily operations. A fun and versatile role that taught me a lot.

2013 - 2014

Svedea Försäkringar

IT-TECHNICIAN

IT-Technician on an insurance company with focus on support and daily operations. I did everything from running the company's servers to supporting the users. A part of the job was also system administration and being available 24/7 from time to time.

2008 - 2011

OneMed AB

SUPERVISOR

I had the role of supervisor for a team of 8, and we were responsible for packing and delivering sterile equipment to hospitals. The job involved managing staff, quality controls, making improvements and administration.

EDUCATION

2023

CodeInstitute

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Six months of full-time fast track education, where I choose React as my specialization field. During the course, we had five portfolio jobs with various tasks, everything from Django, building APIs to a crud operational website with React.

2011 - 2013

Jensen Education YH

IT-TECHNICIAN

Two years of education to become an IT Technician with IT safety as a primary skill.